{
    "id": "9fb96ed16feb4b5fbc6db891bde73be0",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The invaders ………………………………. the countryside.",
            "description": "To ravage is to cause widespread damage.",
            "answers": [
                "ravished",
                "ravaged"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The opera ………………………. the audience.",
            "description": "Ravish can mean fill with delight.",
            "answers": [
                "ravaged",
                "ransacked",
                "ravished"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You look simply ………………………….",
            "description": "Ravishing means delightful.",
            "answers": [
                "ravishing",
                "ravaging"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………………  materials arrived at the factory by the trainload.",
            "description": "Raw means unrefined.",
            "answers": [
                "raw",
                "row"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They are going to ………………………….. this building to make way for the new highway.",
            "description": "Raze means demolish or dismantle.",
            "answers": [
                "race",
                "raze",
                "rage"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… of cheap perfume.",
            "description": "Reeks means smells.",
            "answers": [
                "reeks",
                "wreaks",
                "reaks"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Robin Hood is said to have lived during the ………………………………. of King Richard Lionheart and King John.",
            "description": "Reign means rule.",
            "answers": [
                "rains",
                "reigns",
                "reins"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Hold on to the ……………………… tightly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reins",
                "reigns",
                "rains"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must learn to ………………………. your tongue.",
            "description": "To rein is to check or control.",
            "answers": [
                "rein",
                "reign",
                "rain"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my ………………………….. is coming for dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "relatives",
                "relations",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a small ………………………… but quickly made up.",
            "description": "Row means quarrel or dispute.",
            "answers": [
                "raw",
                "row"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They sat in the front ..................................",
            "description": "Row means the line of seats.",
            "answers": [
                "raw",
                "row"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}